[{"id": 1899, "question": "Mary Master man, a senior at West Moore High School in prefix = st1 /Oklahoma City, was named the winner Tuesday of the annual Intel Science Talent Search. More than 1,700 high school seniors across the nation entered the competition, which is in its 66th year. Spectrographs, which measure wave lengths, are used in research such as astronomy and medicine and in industry. For example, they can be used as a sensing equipment to look for explosives or drugs or to help determine how old an art work is through its powders. They can cost as much as $100,000, but Masterman's invention--made of lenses, a laser, aluminum tubing and a camera--cost less than $1,000, Intel said. Masterman received the honor from Intel Corp. Chairman Craig Barrett during a banquet Tuesday night inWashington. \"It was a ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, Masterman received the honor because", "options": ["the spectrograph she invents can be used to look for drugs", "Masterman's invention is made of lenses, a laser, and a camera", "Masterman has shown great interest in science since she was young.", "the spectrograph she invents costs much less as well as its high quality"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2006, "question": "Several years ago I worked in an office, which had a locust tree growing outside the window. It had grown into a tall tree and must have been there for a long time. The tree blocked the view and made the office seem dull, unfortunately this happened to be the room assigned to me and I was depressed by it for quite some time. When the first spring came, everything was green except the locust tree. Secretly, I was very happy because I had thought it had died. One morning when I opened the window for fresh air, I unexpectedly smelt a familiar sweet scent floating into my office but I couldn't name it. Suddenly, I realized it was the locust tree! The tree that I thought dead was blossoming in full glory. From then on, I usually came to the office very early to see dew forming on the locust tre...\n\nQ: At first the author felt depressed because of the following reasons except that   _  .", "options": ["The tree blocked the view", "the tree made the office seem dull", "When the first spring came, everything was green except the locust tree", "The office was assigned to him"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2683, "question": "Due to climate change, Arctic ice is breaking up earlier in the spring, and its area is decreasing. This is creating problems for polar bears that make their homes off northern Alaska and in Hudson Bay. Polar bears off Alaska normally hunt and raise their young on ice sheets that float on the ocean. But as the ice has melted, the polar bears have been forced to spend more time on land. There, they have begun to frequent beaches, feeding on the remains of whales caught by native hunters. For polar bears, this food is less nutritious than seals that they normally catch on ice sheets. The shrinking ice has also forced more polar bears into the ocean. In the past, they only had to swim short distances between ice sheets. But as the ice has shrunk, polar bears have been forced to swim longer an...\n\nQ: What do polar bears in Hudson Bay do during the summer?", "options": ["They claim territory .", "They protect mates.", "They hunt animals.", "They stop feeding"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 777, "question": "Being able to experience a different environment and custom will give us a new perspective on everything we thought we knew and understood. Maybe, going abroad is an opportunity to look again at not only the country and the people who live there but also ourselves. I had never expected to visit Paris. The French culture didn' t interest me that much, and Paris seemed too big, too touristy, too much. But when I found myself standing next to the Opera National de Paris, completely alone and totally lost, I knew I was in for an interesting ride. I had decided to take a summer history class abroad, and Paris just happened to be where it was set. My teacher eventually found me and other jet-lagged students and walked us down to where we would be staying. Even then, tired, hungry, and feeling di...\n\nQ: By mentioning the uselessness of the watch, the author probably wants to prove   _", "options": ["time in Paris is not worth counting", "he enjoys the time in Paris very much", "life seems meaningful without time", "he has to spend a long time to visit the big city"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2866, "question": "Be Healthy! Be Slim! Be Beautiful! Discover the secret for a Healthy, Slim, Beautiful You! Discover how to be Healthy, Slim and Beautiful! I love this healthy diet program because it helps you lose weight, lose inches, feel healthy and look beautiful. This healthy diet is an 8-week program which is unlike other diet regimes because it focuses on proper nutritional first and weight loss second. Your body must have proper levels of minerals, vitamins, and protein in order to work well. It provides a simply lifestyle change to give you more energy and improve your health most greatly. It offers control over stomach and continuing hunger with a calorie dense diet allowing 1,700 to 2,000 calories a day. If a person has a weight problem their body probably is not working at proper levels of basi...\n\nQ: What is the aim of this diet program?", "options": ["To keep healthy first and to lose weight second.", "To lose weight as much as possible.", "To lose weight at the cost of the health.", "To lose weight first and to keep healthy second."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2170, "question": "Mark Twain left school when he was twelve. He had little school education. In spite of this, he became the most famous writer of his time. He made millions of dollars by writing. His real name was Samuel Langhorne Clemens, but he is better known to all over the world as Mark Twain, his penname. Mark Twain was born in 1835 and he was not a healthy baby. In fact, he was not expected to live through the first winter. But with his mother's care, he managed to survive. As a boy, he caused much trouble for his parents. He used to play jokes on all his friends and neighbors. He didn't like to go to school, and he often ran away from home. He always went in the direction of the nearby Mississippi. He was nearly drowned nine times. After his father's death, Mark Twain began to work for a printer, w...\n\nQ: In order to make a living, Mark Twain   _  .", "options": ["did many kinds of work", "first worked as a printer", "wrote stories in the beginning", "joined the army after he worked in a mine"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 163, "question": "There is no doubt about it.The best way to learn new words is to do it unconsciously.I don't mean while you're unconscious.I mean while you are unconscious of the fact that it is sinking in. That is how I learnt the 30,000 words in my vocabulary by living in an English-speaking world, mother tongue.I just pick them up.But some of _ may be misunderstood.Now, to misunderstand does not mean not to understand.To misunderstand is to understand but incorrectly. The 5 % mislearnt of all the words we \"know\" will be the least frequently used words, as the more frequently used words are less likely to be mislearnt.Some of the misunderstandings may live with all our lives, without knowing that we got them wrong. Many English teachers think that this natural method of learning words in one's own mothe...\n\nQ: It can be inferred that   _  .", "options": ["when somebody is conscious, he or she usually can't learn new words by heart", "we must use the words as often as possible in order to master them", "it's the best way to learn new words that one should only guess their meanings from the context", "only dictionaries can help us learn language well"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2218, "question": "Davey wanted to play baseball. But fifty years ago, in his small town, he couldn't find enough players for two full teams or an empty lot big enough for a field. And when he played ball in his back yard, he just broke windows and got into trouble. So Davey began playing with a plastic golf ball and a broom handle for a bat. When his dad, David Mullaney, a former semi-pro baseball pitcher , realized his son was hurting his arm trying to throw curves with the little plastic ball, he decided to find a better solution. Mullaney got a bunch of hollow plastic _ from a local factory, sat down at his kitchen table and began cutting different size holes in the balls with a razor knife. He thought maybe the holes would alter the ball's flight and help his son throw curves and sliders without hurting...\n\nQ: All the following are true EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["Davey was a good ballplayer after the Wiffle ball came into existence", "David Mullaney wanted to run the family business on his own", "Mullaney's family made a big fortune through the production of Wiffle balls", "Mullaney's business was nearly bought out but they worked hard to keep it"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2002, "question": "A new report says the number of foreign students at colleges and universities in the United States increased by three percent last year. This has been the first obvious increase since 2001. American schools last fall had 583,000 foreign students. The record is 586,000. That was set in 2002 after many years of gains. But after that the numbers fell. The terrorist attacks on September 11th, 2001 led to more visa requirements. Now stronger efforts are being made to get more foreign students to study in the United States. China remained in second place in front of South Korea but behind India, whichsent almost 84,000 students last fall. The number of Japanese fell sharply by nine percent, although it remained in fourth place. There were three percent drops from Indonesia and Kenya, the only Af...\n\nQ: Which subject is the most attractive to foreign students in the USA?", "options": ["Business and management.", "History.", "Engineering.", "Language."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3121, "question": "As part of an effort to improve treatments for life-threatening illnesses, a team of scientists have created rabbits that glow in the dark. The efforts have produced two rabbits out of a litter of eight that went from being a normal, soft white to glowing green in the dark. The rabbits were born at the University of Istanbul as part of the cooperation between scientists from universities in Turkey and Hawaii. The rabbits glow to show that a genetic operation technique can work efficiently. \"The green is not important at all--it's just a marker to show the experiment can be done successfully,\" said University of Hawaii associate professor, Stefan Moisyadi. To produce the glowing effect, researchers injected jellyfish DNA into a mother rabbit's embryos. Then those embryos were put into the m...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the researchers' next goal of the experiment is the creation of a glowing   _  .", "options": ["cockroach", "cat", "rabbbit", "sheep"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 70, "question": "School is out for the summer in some areas, and for many children, that means weeks of sleeping in late, trips to the swimming pool or hours spent in front of the TV. These months of inactivity--- away from the daily tiring things of school--- are something that young people look forward to, but it can have a detrimental influence on the knowledge they have. Studies have shown that children lose a lot in math skills during the summer months. Children who spend little time learning experience a much greater amount of learning loss than those who often take part in summer programs. So when school starts again in the fall, teachers often have to spend several weeks reteaching children material that they have forgotten. Experts suggest that parents make sure the summer months are a time of con...\n\nQ: might be most interested in this passage.", "options": ["Students", "Teachers", "Parents", "Reporters"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1718, "question": "Computer technology is still developing rapidly. The computer of the future will continue to increase in value and performance while decreasing in cost. It will become smaller, but faster and more powerful. It is possible to make some guesses about what the future of the computer will look like, based upon the types of technologies that are being developed now. A lot of progress has already been made in some of these new technologies, but some are still in their earliest stages and may not be ready for use for years. Two of the most interesting areas of computing that are currently being developed are quantum computing and nanotechnology . Quantum computing is one possibility for the future of the computer that could make computers run far faster than even the quickest computers do today. ...\n\nQ: Which of the following can NOT describe the computer of the future properly?", "options": ["Much smaller.", "Much faster.", "More powerful.", "Less valuable."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2669, "question": "One day while shopping in a small town in southern California,it was my misfortune to be approached by a clerk whose personality conflicted with mine. He seemed most unfriendly and not at all concerned about my intended purchase. I bought nothing,and marched angrily out of the store. My hostility toward that clerk increased with each step. On the outside,standing by the road,was a darkskinned young man in his early twenties. His expressive brown eyes met and held mine,and in the next instant a beautiful, dazzling smile covered his face. I gave way immediately. The magnetic power of that smile dissolved all bitterness within me,and I found the muscles in my own face happily responding . \"Beautiful day,isn't it?\"I remarked,in passing. Then,I turned back.\"I really owe you a debt of gratitude ...\n\nQ: The author asked the woman to say \"Thank you!\" to the young man because the young man  _  .", "options": ["had helped the author before", "taught the author how to smile", "was a kind employee of the store", "taught the author a valuable lesson"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1876, "question": "It's fun to receive presents. It also feels good to give presents to others. So what's the best way to budget your money, shop wisely and spend smartly this holiday season? Time for kids asked for advice from Susan Beacham of Money Savvy Generation, a company that teaches money-management skills to kids. \" My first tip is to make a list and check it twice,\" says Beacham. She suggests that kids talk with their families about whom to include in their gift giving and how much to spend. Start by writing down names, Beacham says. Then put a dollar amount next to each name and add it up. Do you have enough money? If not, make changes. And don't forget---- not everyone needs a store-bought gift. Beacham points out that some of the best presents are free. Add to your list the names of people you w...\n\nQ: Which of the following is Beacham's gift idea for friends?", "options": ["Writing a note telling them you love them.", "Offering to help them with their studies.", "Bringing them delicious food.", "Drawing pictures for them"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 85, "question": "Many people hate wet, sticky August, but to some, it's an especially bitter time. A new working paper finds that, March and August are the months in which divorce filings peak. For the paper, the University of Washington's Brian Serafini and Julie Brines analyzed the most recent years of divorce filings in Washington and drew their conclusion: divorce rises sharply in March and August. The result is supported by some nation-wide, anecdotal evidence. Online searches for \"divorce\" and \"child custody\" dramatically grow early in the year, peaking in March, they point out. The authors guess that unhappily married couples schedule their divorce filings around both the winter holidays and Valentine's Day, as well as summer vacations. (More Americans vacation m July than any other month.) There ar...\n\nQ: According to Brian and Julie, why does divorce rise in March and August?", "options": ["People need time to decide and prepare before they divorce.", "Many couples want to have a new beginning in a new year.", "Kids are less involved in winter and summer vacations.", "Couples see more marital problems in their vacation trips."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2684, "question": "Due to climate change, Arctic ice is breaking up earlier in the spring, and its area is decreasing. This is creating problems for polar bears that make their homes off northern Alaska and in Hudson Bay. Polar bears off Alaska normally hunt and raise their young on ice sheets that float on the ocean. But as the ice has melted, the polar bears have been forced to spend more time on land. There, they have begun to frequent beaches, feeding on the remains of whales caught by native hunters. For polar bears, this food is less nutritious than seals that they normally catch on ice sheets. The shrinking ice has also forced more polar bears into the ocean. In the past, they only had to swim short distances between ice sheets. But as the ice has shrunk, polar bears have been forced to swim longer an...\n\nQ: In which publication would you most likely find this passage?", "options": ["Medical News", "Society Today", "Wildlife Journal", "Design Magazine"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1722, "question": "Money might not grow on trees, but scientists have confirmed that gold is found in the leaves of some plants. Researchers from Australia say that the presence of the particles in an eucalyptus tree's leaves indicates that deposits are buried many meters below. They believe that the discovery offers a new way to locate the valuable metal in difficult-to-reach locations. Dr. Mel Lintern from Australia's Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization (CSIRO) said, \"We've found a lot of the easy deposits in Australia in this way. Now we are trying to find the more difficult ones that are buried tens of meters below. And the trees are providing us with a method to be able to do this.\" Using the Australian synchrotron - a vast machine that uses X-rays to explore matter in remarkabl...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be the best title of the passage?", "options": ["A new ways to locate metal deposits is found.", "Gold is found in many trees in Australia.", "Gold in trees can lead to hidden deposits.", "Dr. Mel Lintern discovered new gold deposits."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3001, "question": "Events Calendar TUESDAY Landscape Pests Learn to identify, control and prevent seasonal landscape-disease and landscape-pest problems at the workshop, 3:30 pm. - 5 pm. Tuesday at the US National Arboretum, 3501 New York Ave NE, Washington. $15; registration required. 202-245-4521 or www.usna.usda.gov. THROUGH AUGUST 3 Horticultural Art Watercolors, pen-and-ink drawings and colored-pencil pieces by the Brookside Gardens School of Botanical Art and Illustration will be on display at the exhibit Botanic 2007: The Art and Science of Plants at Brookside Gardens Visitors Center, 1800 Glenallan Ave, Wheaton, through Aug. 3. Free. 301-962-1400 or www.brooksidegardens.org. THROUGH SEPTEMBER 9 Botanical Art Visit Patterns in Nature, an exhibit by Amy Lamb featuring photographs of flowers, leaves and...\n\nQ: If you want to record your name for an event in advance, you may call   _  .", "options": ["202-225-8333", "202-245-4521", "301-962-1400", "202-200-8956"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2506, "question": "No one knows for certain why people dream, but some dreams misht be connected to the mental processes that help us learn. In a recent study, scientists found a connection between nap-time dreams and better memory in people who were learning a new skill. \"I was astonished by this finding,\" Robert Stickgold told Science News. He is a cognitive neuroscientist at Harvard Medical School who worked on the study of-how the brain and nervous system work, and cognitive studies look at how people learn and reason. So a cognitive neuroscientist may study the brain processes that help people learn. In the study, 99 college students between the ages of 18 and 30 each spent an hour on a computer, trying to get through a virtual maze . The maze was difficult, and the study participants had to start in a ...\n\nQ: It is a cognitive scientists job to study  _  .", "options": ["how people dream and learn", "the structure of the nervous system", "whether someone is reasonable", "the process of understanding"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1054, "question": "Mrs. Allen's husband died ten years ago when her son and daughter were still in high school. Mr. Allen had left some money, and since Mrs. Allen had managed a bookstore before she was married, she took the money and bought a shop in town. Later she moved the shop out to the shopping center. She was a pleasant woman; she worked hard and was well-informed about books, and so the bookstore prospered and she was able to hire a friend to help her. Laura Barnes, Mrs. Allen's friend and assistant, was also a widow. She had some free time and the need for a little extra-money, and so she took the job in the bookstore. She was too clever and friendly, and the two women were well-known in the neighbourhood as \"Mrs. A\"and \"Mrs. B\"....\n\nQ: The bookstore prospered   _  .", "options": ["after Mrs. Allen lost control of it", "before Mrs. A got to know Mrs. B", "because the two women had little housework to do", "because Mrs. A became expert at management and threw herself into it"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2008, "question": "Several years ago I worked in an office, which had a locust tree growing outside the window. It had grown into a tall tree and must have been there for a long time. The tree blocked the view and made the office seem dull, unfortunately this happened to be the room assigned to me and I was depressed by it for quite some time. When the first spring came, everything was green except the locust tree. Secretly, I was very happy because I had thought it had died. One morning when I opened the window for fresh air, I unexpectedly smelt a familiar sweet scent floating into my office but I couldn't name it. Suddenly, I realized it was the locust tree! The tree that I thought dead was blossoming in full glory. From then on, I usually came to the office very early to see dew forming on the locust tre...\n\nQ: The reason the author came to the office early is   _  .", "options": ["to enjoy the dew", "to finish her work early", "to do some cleaning", "to avoid the burning sun"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1714, "question": "Healthy relationships are fun and make you feel good about yourself. The relationships that you make in your teenage years will be a special pan of your life. They will teach you some of the most important lessons about who you are. This may help you understand different kinds of relationships, what makes each relationship special, and how to communicate in a positive way. What makes a relationship healthy? Communication and Sharing: The most important part of any healthy relationship between two people is being able to talk and listen to each other. You and the other person can find out what your common interests are. You can share your feelings with the other person and trust that he or she will be there to listen to you and support you. In healthy relationships, people don't lie. Commun...\n\nQ: To have a healthy relationship, you shouldn't   _  .", "options": ["talk and listen to each other", "have common interests", "disagree and quarrel with each other", "take as much as you give"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 577, "question": "There are three main forms of public transport in Singapore--trains,buses and taxis. TRAINS Trains run from 6:00 am to midnight. Single trip tickets start at 80 cents. If you buy an EZ-Link card for $ 15,you can ride the trains and buses as you like. If you need more infor-mation, just call Train Station at 6222 5165. BUSES There are several bus services in Singapore and fares start at 80 cents. Be sure always to ask the driver the cost of your ticket as he can't give change. If you need help,just call Tran-sit Link at 1800 767 4333. TAXIS There are three main taxi companies--City Cab (6552 2222),Comfort (6552 1111) and Tibs (6552 8888). Booking can also be easy by calling the numbers listed above. RENTAL CARS Driving in Singapore is a pleasure and if you like to travel at your own pace,re...\n\nQ: What do we know about traveling in Singapore from the text?", "options": ["A foreigner has no trouble finding his way around.", "It's much cheaper to go around by bus than by train.", "To see a lot in Singapore we have to rent a car.", "It's very easy for visitors to travel in Singapore."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1384, "question": "Do you want to be a successful person? Would you like to know how successful people usually think and what drives them? Here I am going to tell you the key to success that successful people share. First of all, successful people never blame someone or something outside of themselves for their failure to move ahead. They realize that their future lies in their own hands. They understand that they can't control things in life, such as nature, the past and other people. At the same time, they are well aware that they can control their own thoughts and actions. They take responsibility for their life. Perhaps what most separates successful people from others is that they live life \"on purpose\" --- they are doing what they believe they are put here to do. In their opinion, having a purpose in t...\n\nQ: Which is NOT the key to success that successful people share?", "options": ["Taking responsibility for their life.", "Never giving up easily.", "Having a goal in life.", "Controlling things in life."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 251, "question": "They can be seen more frequently than ever before on college campuses, wearing thick-rimmed glasses while listening to indie music. One might find them playing unusual musical instruments, shopping at second-hand stores or expressing themselves in other unique ways. They call themselves hipsters. Being \"hip\" used to mean following the latest fashion. But gradually the word has evolved into a synonym for \"cool\". Hipsters value independent thinking, progressive politics, an appreciation of creativity and intelligence. Hipsters take pains and pride in not being mainstream. However, their culture has become quite trendy. This irony is central to their culture and offers an interesting paradox. \"I do take things in the mainstream with a grain of salt,\" says Ben Polson, a college student at Brow...\n\nQ: Leopold refuses to classify herself as a hipster because  _  .", "options": ["she doesn't like her own unconventional tastes", "there are too many specialized brands, stores and music for the hipster position", "she thinks that a lot of people that are self-defined hipsters aren't really hipsters", "the hipsters' culture has become quite trendy"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1251, "question": "Sons who have fond childhood memories of their fathers are more likely to be emotionally stable in the face of day-to-day stresses, according to psychologists who studied hundreds of adults of all ages. \"As our study shows, fathers do play a unique and important role in the mental health of their children much later in life,\" psychology professor Melanie Mallers of California State University said. For this study, 912 adult men and women between the ages of 25 and 74 completed short daily telephone interviews about that day's experiences over an eight-day period. The interviews focused on the participants' psychological and emotional distress (i.e.whether they were nervous, sad, etc.) and if they had experienced any stressful events that day. The participants were also required to answer q...\n\nQ: What do we know about the study from the passage?", "options": ["It paid close attention to the effect of fathers on their children.", "912 children and adults took part in the study.", "It lasted as long as several months.", "It was funded by the California State University."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 946, "question": "Recipients of this year's Annenberg scholarships were announced on June 19. Brittany Blythe was one of them. In seventh grade,Brittany Blythe dreamed of being a cheerleader . Her school's coaches were less than enthusiastic. \"They said. 'I don't know how you'll be able to do it'. \"she recalls. \"'You won't be able to do it'.\" But Brittany,now a junior at Strath Haven High School near Philadelphia,refused to give up. And when the junior school cheerleaders won a tournament last year, she was right there,dancing and cheering with the rest of the team. Not bad for someone whose legs were cut off below the knee when she was two years old. Brittany,18,was born without shinbones --\"just blood and muscle tissue,\"as she puts it. When she tried to walk, her legs twisted. After the operation, she ada...\n\nQ: What was Brittany's reaction after the operation?", "options": ["She abandoned herself to self-pity.", "She refused to use the prostheses.", "She accepted the result and tried to get used to it.", "She challenged the children who laughed at her."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 671, "question": "Two new studies have investigated why fewer women, compared to men, study and work in the so-called STEM subjects in the United States: science, technology, engineering and mathematics. The American Association of University Women(AAUW) examined existing research. Its report \"Why So Few?\" suggested ways to interest more girls and women in the STEM fields. The researchers found that cultural and environmental factors make a difference. Researcher Christianne Corbett says more boys than girls score very high on math tests in most countries, but Iceland and Thailand are exceptions. \"This is something that we point out in our report--that cultural factors and societal factors can make a difference in who achieves at the very high levels and whether girls are achieving or not.\" Another study ca...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true about the situation in Iceland and Thailand?", "options": ["Boys score higher in math tests than girls.", "Girls are given more exceptional attention than boys.", "More girls score higher in math than boys.", "Boys are more creative than girls."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 821, "question": "Long after the 1998 World Cup was won, disappointed fans were still cursing the disputed refereeing decisions that denied victory to their team. A researcher was appointed to study the performance of some top referees. The researcher organized an experimental tournament involving four youth teams. Each match lasted an hour, divided into three periods of 20 minutes during which different referees were in charge. Observers noted down the referees' errors, of which there were 61 over the tournament. Converted to a standard match of 90 minutes, each referee made almost 23 mistakes, a remarkably high number. The researcher then studied the videotapes to analyse the matches in detail. Surprisingly, he found that errors were more likely when the referees were close to the incident. When the offic...\n\nQ: The word \"officials\" (Para. 4) most probably refers to   _  .", "options": ["the researchers involved in the experiment", "the inspectors of the football tournament", "the referees of the football tournament", "the observers at the site of the experiment"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1057, "question": "They may be small and not able to speak, but babies are proving their amazing cleverness. Scientists began finding infants' skills are more than they are supposed to be. _ Speaking of music, babies can't seem to resist it. Not only are their ears turned to the beats, babies can actually dance to the music. To test babies' dancing ability, the researchers played recordings of classical music, rhythmic beats and speech to infants, and recorded the results. They also invited professional dancers to analyze how well the babies matched their movements to the music. The babies moved their arms, hands, legs feet and heads in response to the music, much more than to the speech. The finding suggests this dancing ability is innate in humans, though the researchers aren't sure why _ becomes weaker la...\n\nQ: The experiment with 26 sleeping infants prove that  _  .", "options": ["babies can learn even while asleep", "babies can respond to the world around them", "babies can tighten their eyelids in response to the sound", "babies can communicate with others while asleep"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2547, "question": "Hi, everybody. On Friday, I had a discussion with working women in Rhode Island about the economic challenges they face in their own lives--challenges shared by many of you. Thanks to the work we've all put in, our economy has come a long way these past six years. Over the past 55 months, our businesses have added 10.3 million new jobs. For the first time in six years, the unemployment rate is below 6 percent. And on Thursday, we learned that over the past six months, our economy has grown at its fastest pace since 2003. But the gains of a growing economy aren't yet felt by everyone. So we've got to harness this momentum , and make the right choices so that everyone who works hard can get ahead. In recent weeks, I've talked about these choices, from raising the minimum wage to creating new...\n\nQ: Which is the true fact according to the passage?", "options": ["During the last half year, our economy has grown fastest since 2003.", "All of us have felt the gains of a growing economy.", "We have never fires any women because of her taking too many bathroom breaks.", "The local businesses will not benefit a lot because of the increase in the minimum wage."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1376, "question": "Facebook users may feel socially successful in the web world but they are more likely to perform poorly in exams. The majority of students who use Facebook every day are doing badly compared with those who don't. About 83% of British 16 to 24-year-old people are using social networking site such as Facebook and MySpace, to keep in touch with friends and organize their social activities. \"Our study shows people who spend more time on Facebook spend less time studying,\" said Aryn Karpinski, a researcher. \"Every generation has its distractions , but I think Facebook is a unique phenomenon.\" Karpinski and a colleague questioned 219 US undergraduates and graduates about their study and general Internet use, as well as their specific use of Facebook. They found 65% of Facebook users accessed the...\n\nQ: Facebook users check their account frequently to   _  .", "options": ["spend less time on study", "make sure new messages aren't missed", "practise specific use of Facebook", "accumulate amount of time spent on Facebook."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 450, "question": "Good Teachers A language training school at Yayuncun needs two full-time teachers and three part-time teachers to teach adults, 12 students a class, oral English and business English during afternoons and evenings. Full-time teachers 25--30 hours per week, 10 000--2 000 yuan per month. Part-time teachers can choose the class to teach, 100--150 yuan per hour, according to your experience. Need native English speakers with teaching experience. Please send your RESUME and PICTURE to eslchina@ yahoo.com.cn Writers/Researchers Currently, Fisher's Travel SOS is looking for the freelance writer and researcher with experience in journalism and the ability to computers, it is part-time positions for our project that will take a month to complete. Work is conducted at home, and will take a couple of...\n\nQ: If you want to get a job that you can do at home you should get in touch with  _", "options": ["jobs@ china&co, com. Cn", "eslchina@ yahoo, com. cn", "dacfxa@ 163bj. Com", "daniellechu@ fisherstravelsos, com"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 501, "question": "Now some women are spending a weekend at Mother's Camp . There, husbands and children are not allowed. Why would a woman want to take a vacation without her family? Some women say they need time to be alone. At Mother's Camp a woman has room to herself. She can sleep, read or watch TV, and no one will bother her. No children will ask,\"Mom, what's for dinner?\" No husband will say, \"Oh, dear, I can't find any clean socks.\"In fact almost 50% of women in the United States work outside the home. Many of them work full-time and then come home to a second job-taking care of their homes and families. These working women say one of their biggest problems is housework. In the United States, working wives do about 75% of the housework. Many of their husbands say they want to help. But then they burn ...\n\nQ: From this passage we can see in the United States.", "options": ["women want to work outside the home", "working wives do most of the housework", "husbands do as much housework as their wives", "women do not like to stay at home with their families"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 54, "question": "\"What is the most important thing you've done in your life?\" The question was put to me during a presentation I gave to a group of lawyers. The answer came to me in an instant. It's not the one I gave, because the situation was not right. As a lawyer in the entertainment industry, I knew the audience wanted to hear some amusing stories about my work with well-known people, but here's the true answer: The most important thing I've ever done occurred on October 8,1990. I began the day playing tennis with an old friend I hadn't seen for a while. Between points we talked about what had been happening in each other's lives. He and his wife had just had a baby boy, who was keeping them up at night. While we were playing, a car came screaming up the road toward the courts. It was my friend's fath...\n\nQ: The author learned from his own experience that   _   .", "options": ["what is taught in school is usually of no use.", "a lawyer cannot learn much in classrooms", "a lawyer should know people's feeling first", "he needs to be able to feel as well as think logically"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2441, "question": "Most of us spend our lives seeking the natural world.We go fishing,sit in the garden,have a picnic,live in the suburbs or go to the seaside.The most popular leisure activity in Britain is going for a walk.When joggers jog,they don't run the streets.Every one of them tend to go to the park or the river. But despite this,our children are growing up nature deprived .I spent my boyhood climbing trees.These days,children are robbed of these ancient freedoms,due to problems like crime,traffic,the loss of the open spaces and strange new ideas about what is best for children,that is to say,things that can be bought,rather than things that can be found. The truth is to be found elsewhere.A study in the US: families had moved to better housing and the children were assessed for ADHD--attention defic...\n\nQ: According to the author,people enjoy   _   to seek nature.", "options": ["jogging on the street", "sitting in the garden", "shopping in the supermarket", "running in the gym"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 736, "question": "When we donate blood, a small amount is usually taken in advance for at least ABO and Rh systems typing. If you are O+, the O is your ABO type and the + is your Rh type. It is possible to be A, B, AB, or O as well as Rh + or Rh-. The ABO system was discovered by Karl Landsteiner in the early 1900s. He was awarded the Nobel Prize for his achievements. There are four basic types of blood in the ABO system: A, B, AB and O. Everybody is born with one of these four types of blood. We get blood type, just like hair color and height from parents. Because of the substances contained in each type, the four groups must be _ carefully, If two different blood types are mixed together, it may put a person into an extremely dangerous situation. Basically, A and B cannot be mixed. A and B cannot receive ...\n\nQ: The text mainly tells us   _  .", "options": ["about the basic types of human blood", "what kind of blood is the most common", "about Karl Landsteiner who won the Nobel Prize", "the relationship between blood type and nationality"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1093, "question": "What does the word \"home\" mean to you? How do you say the word in French? In Spanish? In your language? Although people usually know what the word means, it often has no exact translation. It's not surprising really, because the idea of home differs from country to country, and from person to person. A home is more than a roof and four walls. It's the cooking, eating, talking, playing and family living that go on inside, which are important as well. And at home you usually feel safe and relaxed. But it's not just that homes look different in different countries, they also contain different things and reveal different attitudes and needs. For example, in cold northern Europe, there's a fire in the living room or kitchen and all the chairs face it. In the south, where the sun shines a lot an...\n\nQ: Why is it important to keep the heat out of the houses in southern Europe?", "options": ["Because they want to breathe fresh air outside.", "Because there's a fire in the living room.", "Because they wear heavy clothing all day long.", "Because the sun there shines a lot."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3442, "question": "Nickname: Hawaii's Island of Adventure Size: 4,028 square miles Population: 148,677. The most heavily populated areas are Hilo on the east side and Kailua-Kona on the west. Temperature: Averages between 71degFand 77degF year around ( _ ). Beaches: 47 Golf Courts: 20 Highest Peak: Mauna Kea, 13,796 feet. Agriculture: The bulk of Hawaii's farming products are grown and processed on the Big Island, including coffee, macadamia nuts and papaya. Lodging: 9,655 rooms total; nightly rates range from $35-$5,000. Airports: Hilo International Airport on the east side and Kona International Airport on the west side. Rental Cars: All of the nationally known rental car companies have locations at Hilo International and Kona International Airports as well as many resorts. In addition, Hilo, Kona and the ...\n\nQ: _   are not mentioned as traffic means to get around the Big Island.", "options": ["Trains", "Planes", "Rental cars", "Taxis"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 266, "question": "Over the years, Brian Wansink, director of the Food and Brand Lab at Cornell University, has studied such things as how far Americans typically drive to buy food, how many times we refill our plates at all-you-can-eat buffets and how we organize our kitchens. In the mid-2000s he famously coined the phrase \"mindless eating\"(and wrote a book by that name) to focus attention on all the bad dietary decisions we make without really thinking about them. His new book, Slim by Design: Mindless Eating Solutions for Everyday Life, aims to change the design of restaurants, school lunchrooms, office cafeterias and homes so that the mindless choices we make will be more healthful ones. Some examples: Keep kitchen counters clear. No visible snack food, no bread, no nuts--not even breakfast cereal. In Wa...\n\nQ: According to Wansink, which of the following affects the amount of wine we drink:   _  .", "options": ["the shape of wineglasses", "the color of wineglasses", "the taste of wine", "the quality of wine"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 701, "question": "\"The days when the management in Western companies presented gold watches to long-serving employees to thank them for loyal service is now just a memory.\" says the Educational and Training Support Agency. This new development in the shape and movement of the workforce throughout Western businesses is partly a result of the way that layers of middle management are being removed, leaving more workers responsible for their own development. \"Having workers take responsibility for their own development might be dramatic, but it is now the rule,\" says the Educational and Training Support Agency. \"Today, not only are workers more mobile, they have to run to keep up with changes.\" says the Government-founded agency.\"It is no longer enough for a worker to gain a set of skills.Workers need the abili...\n\nQ: The management in western companies no longer presents gold watches to their employees because   _  .", "options": ["they are not loyal to companies", "other rewards replace gold watches", "the way prove to be a failure", "serving a company for life is rare now"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2080, "question": "Monkeys are very similar to us in many ways. We enjoy watching them because they often act like us. In fact, scientists say monkeys and humans share a common ancestor. Monkeys make us smile, too, because they are creatures full of playful tricks. This is why many monkey expressions are about tricky people or playful acts. One of these expressions is monkeyshines, meaning tricks or foolish acts. So, when a teacher says to a group of students: \"Stop those monkeyshines right now!\", you know that the kids are playing, instead of studying. You might hear that same teacher warn a student not to monkey around with a valuable piece of equipment. You monkey around with something when you are touching or playing with something you should leave alone. Also, you can monkey around when you feel like do...\n\nQ: Which of the following can best state the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["Monkeys are connected with our life.", "Due respect should be paid to monkeys.", "Some English expressions about monkey.", "Monkeys share a common ancestor with us."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 511, "question": "One day Mr. Brown sees a young woman in the street with children. He is very surprised because all the children are wearing the same clothes. White caps, blue coats and yellow trousers. \"Are all these children yours?\" he asks the woman. \"Yes, they are.\" she answers. \"Do you always dress them in the same clothes ?\" asks Mr. Brown. \"Yes,\" answers the mother. \"When we have four children, we dress them in the same clothes because we don't want to lose any of them. It is easy to see our children among other children because they are all wearing the same clothes. And now we have ten, we dress them like this because we don't want to take other children home by mistake. When there are other children among ours, it is easy to see them because their clothes are different....\n\nQ: Why is Mr. Brown surprised? Because   _   .", "options": ["all the children are boys", "all the children are in the same clothes", "all the children are lovely", "all the children are wearing the same trousers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1920, "question": "If you're among the millions of Americans packing their vacation bags for summer trips,don't forget,however, that as soon as you step off the plane,you're expected to follow that country's laws.We took a look at one of the top countries Americans are most likely to visit and what might happen if you got caught. prefix = st1 /Mexico Smoking marijuana:If police find you smoking a cigarette which contains marijuana,they will most likely _ you overnight and you will get a fine. Carrying a firearm:You might be able to walk around with a gun in Texas,but that isn't so in Mexico,so leave your gun behind.If you wish to go hunting in Mexico.you can apply for a gun permit but expect to be charged $5,000.If you are caught bringing a firearm,Mexican policeman may take away your car and arrest you.An a...\n\nQ: If the travelers want to drive in Mexico, they should_.", "options": ["drive on the lower side of the street", "keep an eye out on the radars", "limit their car speed", "pay the fine on the spot"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2223, "question": "While many other teen stars built up their celebrity status by working hard on popular TV shows, Justin shot straight to the top by using social media. A few years ago, Justin uploaded videos of himself on YouTube, showing _ of his favorite songs at home. He just saw it as a bit of fun for friends and family, but when music manager Scooter Braun saw one of the videos, he flew to Justin's hometown of Ontario, Canada to sign him up. Justin was just 13. Shortly after, Justin was flown to the US. He eventually started working with R&B superstar Usher. Justin's first album My world was released in 2009. But all the time, Justin continued to build his fan base on his YouTube account, where some of his original home videos can still be found, and where he continues to post music. \"I wasn't sendin...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["A famous young man", "YouTube---A popular website", "Justin's way to success", "Social media is the most important"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1147, "question": "Thousands of people living in the Chinese capital will celebrate the start of the Chinese New year by heading for the ski resorts . Never mind that Beijing's dry weather seldom produces snow. It is cold enough in winter for snow-making machines to make a covering for the hills north to the capital. And the rapid growth of a pleasure-seeking middle class has formed the basis for this new craze . Since Beijing's first ski resort was opened ten years ago, the sport has enjoyed astonishing increase. There are now more than a dozen resorts. Clothes markets in the city have added bright colored ski suits to their winter collections. Mr. Wei, a manager of a newly-opened ski resort in Beijing, sees the growth of an industry that could soon lead Chinese to head for the ski resorts of Europe. In rec...\n\nQ: What is the main problem in running a ski resort?", "options": ["Difficulty in hiring land.", "Lack of business experience.", "Price wars with other ski resorts", "Shortage of water and electricity."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 331, "question": "HK's Family Affair The 32nd Hong Kong Art Festival, to be held early next year, will be based on the theme of \"family\". The art festival, considered to be Asia's best, began in 1973. \"We hope that people from Beijing and from all over the world will go to Hong Kong to enjoy the multiple performances in our art festival,\"Douglas Gautier, the festival's management director, said in a press conference in the capital. In the 29 days of the festival, which runs from February 8 to March 7, 2004, the audience can choose from 111 performances of 51 programmes staged by 700 foreign performers, 450 local artists and 160 actors from the mainland. Programmes vary from classical music, jazz, world music, Western and Peking opera, drama and dance to outdoor spectaculars. The programmes include Beethoven...\n\nQ: The press conference must have been held   _  .", "options": ["in Hong Kong", "in Europe", "in Beijing", "in England"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1795, "question": "Have you ever wanted to achieve a goal and ended up doing tons of research on how to achieve the goal? As you learn more and more, it feels like you know less and less because when you learn something new, you find that there is a lot to know about those things. Sometimes, people will get stuck in this needing to gather more and more information. There's nothing wrong with learning a lot, but when you let learning get in the way of doing, you will never get going. When you never get going, you still never start having the things you want. Too much learning can paralyze you in terms of taking action. A better way to go about achieving a goal is to gather some information and immediately start taking action on the information you have gathered. Many times you will feel unprepared, and that's...\n\nQ: Why does the author mention how a baby learns to walk?", "options": ["To prove another point is wrong.", "To encourage readers to change.", "To introduce a learning approach.", "To support a conclusion."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3307, "question": "In the 19thcentury, Americans from the eastern states moved out west to settle in the rich new lands along the Pacific Coast. The most difficult part of their trip was crossing \"the Great American Desert\" in the western part of the United States by horse and wagon. The western desert can be very dangerous. There is little water and there are few trees. But the desert also has scenery of great beauty. Tall towers of red and yellow stone rise sharply from the flat, sandy valley floor. The scene has been photographed many times and appears in movies and on TV. In Arizona, man-made dams across the Colorado River have made two large lakes in the middle of the dry desert country. At Lake Powell, the red stone arch of Rainbow Bridge rises high above the blue lake. There are few roads. Many areas ...\n\nQ: In the 1800s, many travelers died in Death Valley because of  _  .", "options": ["illness", "high temperature", "cold weather", "poisonous water"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1240, "question": "Generational differences and the economy are shifting more responsibilities for children from their parents to grandparents, according to a new survey. More than one-third of grandparents aged 50 and older contribute financially to their grandchildren's upbringing, and 11 percent have a grandchild living with them, the poll by AARP, the group for 36 million older US citizens, showed. Forty percent of people who responded to the telephone survey, whose average age was 69, reported spending more than $500 on grandchildren over the past year beyond traditional gifts.Education costs accounted for 53 percent, daily expenses for 37 percent and medical costs for 23 percent.Sixteen percent provided daycare for grandchildren. \"They are the safety net for American families, helping to pay for practi...\n\nQ: What does the author think of the phenomenon mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["Reasonable.", "Unbelievable.", "Acceptable.", "Not given."], "answer": 3}]